[{"answer": "It won't hold, my friend, it won't prove out", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What would do that...", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We can't  a war", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm not sure we can afford to have the", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What's it gonna cost?", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Who would find out", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "...they sound what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What one has to do, Mr. my friend.  Is to fight a holding action", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "If we can hold the brea", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "...holding action.  THEY'RE GOING TO TEAR THIS GUY TO ", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, hut you can't hold the dam.  How the hell, n'nu'n', I don't get what you want  to ..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "String a few together.  All I need's eleven", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What do you think would hold it off", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey, I know that, hey, I'm ... ", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " \"The Country Is At War", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " \"The Country Is At War", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "...Yoha, Yoha... Yoha.  that place", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "They got to have something that we want", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What do we have that they want", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "...who is this guy...", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We don't need an Act Two", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Act Tw", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " And get me the Fad King.  No.  Get him First...  We don't need an Act Two", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We've just got to hold their interest for ten more days, till the Election", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's a teaser, absolutely right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " ...where is the Back End coming from", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The thing with the Yellow Ribbon..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The hostages, but that was a naturall", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "...the Yellow Ribbon, but who, who'd profit from ..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It's a, it's a...  It  be a ribbon..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It can't be a ribbon cause AIDS had a ribbon, cause the Yellow Ribbon thing had a ribbon, cause..", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Y'see,  is what Producing i", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " King, we've got to be on the streets in..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "that place, that place, that place, my friend bond Villains", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend...", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "The hats", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why a beret", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't think you're gonna need it", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "They got the guys on a 'em, but don't lettem touch it... Let'em leave us alone", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "They got the guys on a 'em, but don't lettem touch it... Let'em leave us alone", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What can it hurt is they offend me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " ...hell of a price for the country to pay", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "...what's the Long View", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "...this's ..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Is she saying this in Albanian...", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "S'all very well, but when the Fit hits the Shan, somebody's going to have to Stay After School, and who do you 'spose that might be", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Well, I'm not interested in how long its", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not interested in how long its", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I'm interested in the Security of My Country, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Ask it", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Why do people go to war", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " Loo", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "In the Folk Music Section.  We'll be in in..", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "...this the Guy", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Where is he now", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Some, military... Special Program, that place somewhere..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "They got him standing by", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Ain't  the truth.", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "What am  gonna do?  I'm gonna", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "We pick up my friend.  Sneak him back inside the Beltway. And we plan his homecoming.  Zt's gone be my friend, Dr. my friend, and ...They're gonna forget, they're gonna forget, they're gonna forget that there  an election...The Pres's gonna have to say, one of his speeches,", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " Getting off on the inaugural?  Gonna go..", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "And?  NO.  I don't wanna know.  What do you ", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "What happens if he doesn't have his medication", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "...gimme some help..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "...just want to Get Back to the Beans..", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "We'll deal with that when we come to it.   is producing.   is what they pay off on...come on, Pal, Boots and Saddles..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Shot down, Forced down...  You guys are  it... You're missing th", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "How do we explain ", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "...how do we explain that?  With the World Watching", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " You see, this is what I'm talking about.  Stand It On Its Head.  How does it Work for your benefit..", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "What rig", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Watch me", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Deal's changed", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "my friend.  my friend... you knew the... my friend.  You knew the deal when you signed ", "docId": "wag-the-dog_production.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "No, the deal  changed. You can't ... what is it?  Money?  ?  You want Money", "qsentId": 76}]